Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): - I had a dream, I had a dream, I had a dream. And like I said, this one was clear. I had a dream that Charlie was betrayed. I had a dream and I feel as strongly about the dream that I had that Charlie was betrayed by people closest to him. Never ignore your subconscious. That's why I say, pay attention to my dreams.
Speaker 2: - Have you ever had a dream that...
Speaker 3: - No, you had a dream. Charlie told you he
Speaker 4: was, yeah, Charlie told me.
Speaker 4: that he was betrayed. Charlie was sitting on the patio and he was eating hummus. He's like, "This is the best hummus I've ever tasted in my life."
Speaker 6: I had a dream.
Speaker 5: It was so clear. I promise you, you can actually fact check this with Village Crazy Lady, my girl Mel.
Speaker 7: - You had your, what you could do.
Speaker 8: - Loving your emails telling me about your dreams. People in Turning Point.
Speaker 8: had dreams dreams can give
Speaker 6: you some sort of intuition and i certainly think that mine gave me a lot of intuition oh the cool kids don't pay any
Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): mind when they have a very vivid dream and charlie in the dream says he was betrayed oh the cool good that's so haha it's not cool i have been having a lot of dreams you could you do you what you want candace owens and to try to paint her as a crazy person because she had a dream
Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): And
Speaker 4: I'm sticking with the dream. I'm sticking with the
Speaker 5: dream. Many people actually had dreams and they email me at them all the time. And I had another vivid dream. The dream was so vivid. It was like, if you've ever seen Harry Potter, they're just going on vibes in a dream on
Speaker 1 (higher-pitched voice): the Candace show.
Speaker 4: That's it. She had a dream and now she's just blindly pointing the finger at everybody. Tell me who betrayed you. It
wasn't
Speaker 5: until the third week after his death that finally one face came through in this dream. It came through as clear
Speaker 9: as day. I'm around the corner of the restaurant and...
Speaker 7: You want him to do you so much you could do anything? Sorry,
Speaker 9: that was a dream that I had.